Dhruv Varia

D/34, Yogiraj Township, Waghodia-Dabhoi Ring Road, Vadodara, Gujarat • +91 91047 55373 • dhruvvaria1101@gmail.com • linkedin.com/in/dhruvvaria • https://dv1101.github.io/

ASP.NET/ ASP.NET Core Developer

With over a year of experience in the tech industry, I've honed my skills in Dot Net Framework, ASP.NET, and Oracle 11G DB. A significant part of my career has been spent working at Vadodara Smart City, where I developed a Property Tax Generation and Collection System. This new system has improved data compilation from the old system by 75%, significantly speeding up the process. A standout accomplishment in my career was winning first place at the Tech Expo – PU in the CSE branch. My technical expertise, combined with my ability to deliver high-quality results, makes me a strong candidate in the field

WORK EXPERIENCE

Vadodara Smart City Development Limited • Vadodara, Gujarat, India • 07/2023 - Present **Developer**

• Working on developing Property Tax Generation and Collection System.

Larsen And Toubro Heavy Engineering • Vadodara, Gujarat, India • 07/2021 - 10/2021 Supervisor

 Worked as Supervisor Junior Engineer trainee, My Main role was on Engineer the process of Manufacturing/Fabrication work of Gasifier, Boiler, Heat Exchanger, etc. and supervise the process, Work Allocation to Team Members and passing QA Tests.

EDUCATION

Bachelor's In Technology Computer Science & Engineering

Parul Institute Of Engineering And Technology • Vadodara, Gujarat, India • GPA: 8.10 • 10/2021 - 05/2024

Diploma Mechanical Engineering

Polytechnic, The Maharaja Sayajirao University of Baroda • 06/2018 - 05/2021

Class X

New Heaven Vidyalaya - GSEB • 03/2018

SKILLS

ASP.NET, Bootstrap, C#, Cascading Style Sheet, Hypertext Markup Language, JavaScript, jQuery, .NET, Oracle Database, Process Development, SQL, Stored Procedure

PROJECTS

Property Tax Collection and Management Module for Vadodara Smart City – IDP Project

Vadodara Smart City Development Ltd. • 12/2022 - 04/2024

Objective: Upgrade an outdated system with new technologies and provide robust, fast and secure software for handling and management of 22 lakh+ Properties of Vadodara City.

E-Library Management

Based on ASP.NET and MSSQL

CERTIFICATIONS

Road Traffic Data Analysis using Machine Learning Techniques – 74% Merit

Designing smart traffic surveillance system for reducing traffic congestion and roadside accident mitigation

IOT (Internet of Things) – Elite Category certified

NPTEL - IIT Kharagpur

Azure Fundamentals

Cloud That

AWARDS & SCHOLARSHIPS

Tech Expo 1st Prize CSE BRANCH

Parul University • 02/2024

MYSY Scholarship

Gujarat State Education Board

CMSS Scholarship

Gujarat State Education Board